atmel.com 2014-12-23

# Privacy Policy

## SCOPE

This statement applies to Atmel's worldwide websites hosted on Atmel controlled domains (including atmel.com), as well as other Internet-based services made available by Atmel (each such website and service is referred to in this policy as a "Site"), except in those instances where the applicable Site links to a different Atmel privacy policy.

Your privacy is important to Atmel. This statement discloses the information practices for Atmel's Sites, including the collection and use of personal information that may be collected by Atmel anytime you interact online with Atmel, such as when you visit an Atmel Site, when you purchase Atmel products, literature and/or services, or when you call our sales or support associates in connection with a Site or Atmel product or service provided online. Please take a moment to read the following to learn more about our information practices, including what type of information is gathered, how the information is used and for what purposes, to whom we disclose the information, and how we safeguard your personal information.

## COLLECTION, USE AND SHARING OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION

Atmel may request personal information when you interact with a Site or contact Atmel, including personal information requested: (i) to enable you to register for, access, customize or personalize online resources, communications, marketplaces or communities; (ii) to enable you to purchase or download software, products or services; or (iii) in connection with a job application or inquiry. This information may include your name, mailing address, phone number, email address, contact preferences, and credit card or payment account information.

Atmel also uses personal information collected online to provide additional products, services (e.g. online communities, marketplaces, newsletters, journals, etc.), questionnaires, contests and features that you may have requested (including educational literature and related information about Atmel's business and product resources). We also use personal information: (i) to develop, deliver and improve our products, services and content; (ii) subject to your communication choices, for marketing, sales leads and advertising; and (iii) for internal research and analysis. For example:

  * The Atmel Gallery website and service allows you to browse, search, purchase, download and install extensions for the Atmel Studio software application. When you register as a user, the personal information you provide will be used to process transactions for such extensions and, unless you tell us otherwise, may be used to contact you about future events, newsletters and product developments and other products or services that may be of interest to you.
  * You can enable auto detection of updates to your Atmel Studio software and its installed extensions. When querying for available updates, the Atmel Studio software will send information about your Atmel Studio version (including its ID and the ID of extensions you may be using) and information about your usage and location. Our use of this information will include (i) the identification of available updates; (ii) data analysis regarding usage of our products and services; and (iii) identification of users that may interested in other Atmel products or services.

Personal information about you will be accessible to Atmel, including its affiliates, subsidiaries and groups worldwide, and to individuals and organizations that use personal information solely for and at the direction of Atmel. Also, when you purchase or download third party extensions or software via the Atmel Gallery feature within the Atmel Studio software (or via any related Atmel Gallery Site), your personal information will be provided to that third party to facilitate and fulfil the transaction, including for the purposes of (i) enabling use of the purchased/downloaded extension or software and (ii) to allow the third party to alert you of the expiry of any time-limited software and, in connection with this, to tell you how you can renew or extend your use of this software or how to obtain equivalent, substitute software. Any other use of your information by such third party is subject to the third party’s privacy policy.

Also, note that certain Sites (such as the Atmel Gallery) are structured as marketplaces and/or communities. We may offer features that allow you to connect and communicate in public or semi-public spaces on these Sites, such as product/software reviews, forums and group messaging. Please use common sense and good judgement when posting in these community spaces or sharing your personal information with others on these Sites. Be aware that any personal information you submit there can be read, collected, or used by others, or could be used to send you unsolicited messages. Atmel generally does not remove content from community spaces, and your posts may remain public after your account is closed. You are responsible for the personal information you choose to post in community spaces on the Sites.

You may choose not to provide any personal information to Atmel online by electing not to enter any personal information into a form or data field on any Atmel Site and by not using any personalized services provided by our online resources. Please note, however, that you will not be able to use certain Atmel sites/services without providing personal information.

You may also choose to stop receiving Atmel newsletters, marketing communications and product and service updates at any time by using the contact details at the end of this privacy policy or by following the specific instructions provided in emails that you receive.

## SECURITY OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION

Atmel is committed to protecting the security of your personal information. We use a variety of security measures and procedures to help protect your personal information from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure. For example, we store the personal information you provide using a secured database system. As such, only authorized personnel will have access to personal information stored by Atmel.

## PROTECTION OF CHILDREN'S PERSONAL INFORMATION

Atmel is a general audience website and does not knowingly collect any personal information from children under the age of 13.

## USE OF COOKIES

The Atmel Sites use a technology called cookies. A cookie is a small text file that is placed on your hard disk by a Web page server. For example, cookies can help provide additional functionality to a Site or help us analyze usage of the Site more accurately. Please refer to our Cookies Policy for further details.

## COLLECTION AND USE OF NON-PERSONAL INFORMATION

We also collect non-personal information − data in a form that does not permit direct association with any specific individual. We may collect, use, transfer, and disclose non-personal information for any purpose. For example, we may collect information such as language, zip code, area code, unique device identifier, location, and the time zone where a Site is used or accessed so that we can better understand customer behaviour and improve our products, services, and advertising. If we combine non-personal information with personal information, the combined information will be treated as personal information for as long as it remains combined.

## LINKS TO NON-ATMEL WEB SITES

Atmel Sites may contain links to other websites. Please be aware that Atmel is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave an Atmel Website and to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information.

## YOUR CONSENT TO INTERNATIONAL TRANSFERS OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION

Personal information collected on or via an Atmel Site may be stored and processed in the United States or any other country in which Atmel or its affiliates, subsidiaries, agents or contractors maintain facilities, and by using the Site, you consent to any such transfer of information outside of your country, including to countries which may have no or less stringent privacy laws and to the facilities of third party cloud computing service providers.

## CHANGES TO THIS STATEMENT

Atmel may update this privacy policy at its discretion. We encourage you to periodically review this privacy statement to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect.

Date last updated: November 6, 2012

## DISCLOSURES REQUIRED BY LAW

Please be aware that in certain circumstances, it is possible that personal information may be subject to disclosure pursuant to judicial or other government subpoenas, warrants, or orders.

## CONTACT INFORMATION

Atmel welcomes your comments regarding this privacy statement including requests to update your personal information, to stop receiving newsletters or marketing from Atmel, or your removal from our database. Please direct any questions or concerns to the following contact information provided below:

Atmel Corporation   
Legal Department/Privacy Compliance   
1600 Technology Drive   
San Jose, California 95110

Privacy Policy, ©2011-2012 Atmel Corporation. Website contents, ©1998-2012 Atmel Corporation. All rights reserved. Atmel Corporation, 1600 Technology Drive, San Jose, California 95110, USA.
